Puss in Boots: The Three Diablos is a adventure, animation,
comedy film directed by Raman Hui Shing-Ngai.
Puss in Boots is on a mission to recover the Princess' stolen
ruby from the notorious French thief, Whisperer.
Reluctantly accompanied by three little kittens, Three Diablos,
Puss must tame them before they endanger the mission.
Puss in Boots (voice), played by Antonio Banderas.
Captain Of The Guard / Paolo The Squire (voice), played by Gilles Marini.
Princess Alessandra Bellagamba (voice), played by Charlotte Newhouse.
Food Prisoner (voice), played by Chris Miller.
Water Prisoner (voice), played by Walt Dohrn.
Toilet Paper Prisoner (voice), played by Bret Marnell.
Puss in Boots: The Three Diablos is a 2012 American
animated short adventure comedy film.
It was directed by Raman Hui and features Antonio
Banderas as the voice of the title character.
The short was released on February 24, 2012, attached as a bonus
feature to the Puss in Boots DVD and Blu-ray (3D) release.
The short takes place after the events of the first film and tells a story of Puss in Boots on a
mission to recover a princess' stolen ruby from the notorious French thief the Whisperer.
Reluctantly accompanied by three cute little kittens called the Three
Diablos, Puss must tame them before they endanger the mission.
The tone is lighthearted.